<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>saa c03 on Home</title>
    <link>https://doanhai.dev/tags/saa-c03/</link>
    <description>Recent content in saa c03 on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://doanhai.dev/tags/saa-c03/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>400&#43; Câu hỏi luyện thi chứng chỉ AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate (SAA-C03) - Phần 6</title>
      <link>https://doanhai.dev/certificate/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-saa-c03-exam-practice-questions-part-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doanhai.dev/certificate/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-saa-c03-exam-practice-questions-part-6/</guid>
      <description>Question 1 A manufacturing firm has a large number of smart devices installed in various locations worldwide. Hourly logs from these devices are stored in an Amazon S3 bucket. Management is looking for comprehensive dashboards which should incorporate usages of these devices and forecast usage trends for these devices.
Which tool is the best suited to get this required dashboard?
A. Use S3 as a source for Amazon QuickSight and create dashboards for usage and forecast trends</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>400&#43; Câu hỏi luyện thi chứng chỉ AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate (SAA-C03) - Phần 5</title>
      <link>https://doanhai.dev/certificate/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-saa-c03-exam-practice-questions-part-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doanhai.dev/certificate/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-saa-c03-exam-practice-questions-part-5/</guid>
      <description>Question 1 You have implemented AWS Cognito services to require users to sign in and sign up to your app through social identity providers like Facebook, Google, etc. Your marketing department wants users to anonymously try out the app because the current log-in requirement is excessive, which may reduce the demand for products and services offered through the app. What would you suggest to the marketing department in this regard?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>400&#43; Câu hỏi luyện thi chứng chỉ AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate (SAA-C03) - Phần 4</title>
      <link>https://doanhai.dev/certificate/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-saa-c03-exam-practice-questions-part-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doanhai.dev/certificate/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-saa-c03-exam-practice-questions-part-4/</guid>
      <description>Question 1 A start-up firm has created a cloud storage application that gives users the ability to store any amount of personal data &amp;amp; share them with their connections. For this, they are using Amazon S3 buckets to store user data. The firm has used Amazon S3 multipart upload to upload large objects in parts. During the last quarter, the finance team has observed a surge in storage costs for the S3 bucket.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>400&#43; Câu hỏi luyện thi chứng chỉ AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate (SAA-C03) - Phần 3</title>
      <link>https://doanhai.dev/certificate/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-saa-c03-exam-practice-questions-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doanhai.dev/certificate/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-saa-c03-exam-practice-questions-part-3/</guid>
      <description>Question 1 A global beverage company is using AWS cloud infrastructure for hosting its web application. For a new beverage, the company plans to use a unique voice using Amazon Polly to help market this product to a wide range of customers.
Which feature can be used with Amazon Polly for this purpose?
A. Create custom Lexicons with Amazon Polly
B. Use a custom SSML tag with Amazon Polly
C. Build a Brand Voice using Amazon Polly</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>400&#43; Câu hỏi luyện thi chứng chỉ AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate (SAA-C03) - Phần 2</title>
      <link>https://doanhai.dev/certificate/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-saa-c03-exam-practice-questions-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doanhai.dev/certificate/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-saa-c03-exam-practice-questions-part-2/</guid>
      <description>Question 1 An online hypermarket company has deployed a web application using a REST API with Amazon API Gateway. Recently, they upgraded the backend to make the API scalable. After the upgrade, it was discovered that some consumers using older methods could no longer access the API, as the older method is not compatible with the responses from the backend.
How should a solutions architect redesign the API Gateway to ensure compatibility with the old method?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>400&#43; Câu hỏi luyện thi chứng chỉ AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate (SAA-C03) - Phần 1</title>
      <link>https://doanhai.dev/certificate/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-saa-c03-exam-practice-questions-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doanhai.dev/certificate/aws-certified-solutions-architect-associate-saa-c03-exam-practice-questions-part-1/</guid>
      <description>Question 1 A large engineering company plans to deploy a distributed application with Amazon Aurora as a database. The database should be restored with a Recovery Time objective (RTO) of one minute when there is a service degradation in the primary region. The service restoration should incur the least admin work.
What approach can be initiated to design an Aurora database to meet cross-region disaster recovery requirements?
A. Use Amazon Aurora Global Database and use the secondary region as a failover for service degradation in the primary region</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
