<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>patroni on Home</title>
    <link>https://doan-hai.github.io/tags/patroni/</link>
    <description>Recent content in patroni on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 23:48:05 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://doan-hai.github.io/tags/patroni/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cài đặt và cấu hình PostgreSQL Cluster với Patroni cho môi trường Production</title>
      <link>https://doan-hai.github.io/database/install-and-configure-postgresql-cluster-with-patroni-for-production-environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 23:48:05 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doan-hai.github.io/database/install-and-configure-postgresql-cluster-with-patroni-for-production-environment/</guid>
      <description>Bài viết này hướng dẫn cách thiết lập một PostgreSQL Cluster với tính sẵn sàng cao (HA - High Availability) trên môi trường production. Chúng ta sẽ sử dụng các công cụ như Patroni, Etcd, HAProxy và Keepalived để đảm bảo hệ thống luôn hoạt động ổn định, có khả năng failover tự động và cân bằng tải hiệu quả.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Câu hỏi luyện thi chứng chỉ AWS Certified Solutions Architect Associate (SAA-C03) - Phần 1</title>
      <link>https://doan-hai.github.io/certificate/saa-c03-certification-exam-review-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 23:48:05 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doan-hai.github.io/certificate/saa-c03-certification-exam-review-questions/</guid>
      <description>Question 1 A large engineering company plans to deploy a distributed application with Amazon Aurora as a database. The database should be restored with a Recovery Time objective (RTO) of one minute when there is a service degradation in the primary region. The service restoration should incur the least admin work.
What approach can be initiated to design an Aurora database to meet cross-region disaster recovery requirements?
A. Use Amazon Aurora Global Database and use the secondary region as a failover for service degradation in the primary region</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Câu hỏi luyện thi chứng chỉ PSM-I - Phần 1</title>
      <link>https://doan-hai.github.io/certificate/psm1-certification-exam-review-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 23:48:05 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://doan-hai.github.io/certificate/psm1-certification-exam-review-questions/</guid>
      <description>1. Which group is required to be at the Sprint Review? (choose the best answer) The Product Owner, the Scrum Master and the Developers. The Product Owner and stakeholders. The Product Owner and Product Lead. The Scrum Team and stakeholders. ✅ The Product Owner, technical leads and stakeholders. Explanation The Sprint Review is an inspect and adapt opportunity for both the Scrum Team and key stakeholders. 2. True or False: The Product Owner is accountable for both maximizing the value of the product and the value of the work done by the Developers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
